[music]
Week 14 in the Motor City was a crucial
NFC showdown with huge playoff implic.
lications between Detroit and Dallas.
Lions remain in the hunt for a
postseason birth with a 44-30 win over
the Cowboys. Welcome into the Detroit
Lions live postgame show presented by
Curado Insurance alongside the Super
Bowl champ Lomus Brown. I'm Danny
Rogers. Detroit's chances of making the
playoffs have now been boosted to 55%.
If the Lions lost tonight, it would fall
below 20%. This was a mustwin game for
Detroit and the Lions answered the bell,
LB.
>> Hey, this was a playoff game, Danny.
This was the first of many that we have
coming up. And man, like you say, where
to answer the bell, Detroit Lions, the
fans, the white out, just everything was
set up for us to come in here and get a
great great victory. And those guys were
so resilient. It was unbelievable. It
was a great game. And I'm glad we got
that victory. Tonight was a heavyweight
match between two of the top offenses in
the NFL. Over 600 combined passing
yards, 74 points later, Detroit contain
Javvante Williams in the run game for
Dallas. Forced Dak Prescott to go to the
air where Detroit picked him off twice.
Big numbers in here. Five sacks for
Detroit. Get this L miss. They had four
five sacks in their last four games.
Five coming tonight. They heard
defensive coordinator Calvin Shepard
when he said, "Do something. Get to the
quarterback this week."
>> I mean, and I love what Calvin Shepard
did too by mixing up his personnel, by
mixing up the schemes a lot. And I mean,
Muhammad, oh MG, Danny came through big
time today. And that's what players do
when you're given that opportunity. You
have to seize the opportunity. He was
one of the many players on the defensive
side of the ball as well as the
offensive side of the ball as well as
special teams to come up with big plays
to help us seal this victory.
>> Defensive end Elquadine Muhammad three
sacks tonight make that nine on the
season. He now leads Detroit in getting
to the quarterback this season. And in
stadium host Anthony Bolino talked with
the big guy post game.
Our fans were down on the field right
now with number 96 Alcad Muhammad. Three
tackles, three sacks, three TFLs, four
quarterback hits, living in the back
field. AQ, what was working for this
pass rush here tonight?
>> I mean, listen, our coach challenged us
early in the in the week. We knew how
important this game was and uh we knew
we had to rush up front to get this to
get this dub and we came out on top. How
about the atmosphere here inside Ford
Field? You know, a global audience
worldwide on Amazon Prime Thursday Night
Football. This place was rocking. It's
amazing.
>> It's nothing better than Detroit.
>> Now, what do you want to tell these fans
here that are that stuck around all the
way to the end? Big- time victory over
the Cowboys. The playoff pushes on. 44
to 30 is the final score. What do you
want to tell these fans?
>> Without these fans, we wouldn't be where
we are. So thank you Detroit
>> fans make some noise for number 96 Al
quadine Muhammad
>> man a few words but they sure do they do
sure sure do work McNeel and Jack
Campbell also getting in on the sack
party tonight Shepard said hey we have
to affect the quarterback if we want our
secondary to play the style of coverage
that they need to play especially
against the number one passing offense
in the NFL in down. [laughter]
>> Excuse me. Pardon me.
>> That guy there, man, that's the voice
that just walked past us. And
>> you [laughter] missed it. Yeah, we have
no proof.
>> I know. But Danny, you are so right. And
we've been talking about it right all
year long that pass coverage and pass
rush, they're tied at the hip. and those
it was ever so more important tonight
because the pressure that they the guys
were able to get up front really helped
those guys in the back field and Calvin
Shepard's right. I mean, we're
predominantly a man coverage team, and
to play man coverage, you can't let
those quarterbacks sit back there and
get comfortable and scan the field. And
man, we g we we pressured Dak Prescott
so much, hit him so much that we got him
off his spot. And that's what we need to
continue to do to the rest of these
quarterbacks that we're going to face.
>> Dan Campbell's going to tell his
defense, "Whatever you ate before this
game, eat it for breakfast, lunch, and
dinner every day from here on out until
those playoffs." Coach Campbell is
standing by at the podium. Let's hear
from him.
>> Um, [cough]
proud of the guys. You know, they uh
they rallied, man. They showed up. Um,
you know, the work was there all week.
It always is. But the, you know, the the
intensity, the urgency, the um, you
know, the guys don't ever get frazzled.
They don't get panicked. They just go to
work. And, uh, they did it again. We
talked about takeaways. Man, we got
takeways. We got three of them. Uh, two
of them turned into 14 points. you know,
we were able to turn those up. Um, and
then the last one, we were able to kneel
it, you know, after, uh, Reed's pick.
So, um, you know, a number of guys
played played really good for us. Um,
you know, Muhammad with the three sacks,
that was big time. You know, Hutch draws
a lot of attention. He got some one-on-
ones, man. He won his 10 one-on- ones.
That was huge. Um, you know, Jack
Campbell was all over the field. Had a
punch out. Um, TK in the return game,
Tom Kennedy was huge for us big time.
And so was Sailors. Special teams played
a huge role. And then golf, man, I told
him we were going to put this on him.
This game we were going to put on him.
And uh it was going to start with him.
And uh man, he really lit the fire for
us. And then St. Brown, man, we didn't
know if we were going to be able to get
him. Uh once again, St. Brown does what
St. Brown does. If he can play, he's
going to play. And uh and and he didn't
want any plays off either, by the way.
Like he's going in to compete. He he'll
block. He made some explosive plays for
us. J Mo stepped up. Um just a number of
great performances. I thought Gibbs
showed up, Demo, Ju the guys we talked
about, man. Uh we challenged a number of
our guys, man, they really showed up for
us. So that's a damn good win. Uh that
team is hot. It was a hot team coming in
here. Uh that's a potent offense. And uh
you know, was it perfect? No. We still
got some stuff that that wasn't good.
You know, we had some of these
penalties. We had some young guys that
uh we got to clean some of this up, you
know, fall start, stuff like that. But
we overcame a lot and uh that's that's
what this team does. So I'm proud of
them. Can
>> you speak to the complimentary effort of
of football game you talked about?
>> That was awesome.
>> Then your offense turning it into
touchdown special teams. When [snorts]
you guys play that well in all three
phases, you got to believe you're pretty
tough to beat, right? Well, that that's
that is one of the that's that game
there is one of the few we've had where
we really played complimentary football.
I mean, really really did, you know. Um,
and to be able to score right before
halftime, we come out, we get the
takeaway. Great job by Barnes. Um, and
then we, you know, we turn it into
points. I mean, that that's that was
huge. You know, all of that the whole
sequence of, you know, just the momentum
and carrying it and helping each other
out. And so uh everything was big and
the guys really stepped up but we did we
played complimentary football and that
above all is what what really makes a
difference. That's what good teams do.
You know it doesn't matter how good your
offense or defense is man if you are not
able to like help each other out when
you need it with one of the phases man
it's it's tough it makes it tough and we
were able to do that today
>> about St. around and and uh you know
when did you decide that he was going to
play? How close was it and how much this
is just presence being on the team? A
ripple effect on everybody else in the
offense.
>> Yeah, it's huge. Well, you know um St.
Brown is what we are. He's what we are.
And uh that guy is where he goes, we go.
and his toughness and uh his willpower,
his desire to compete, to help those
guys around him, to do whatever it takes
to win is second to none. I mean, he is
he's rare, man. His mentality, I mean,
he's got his mindset is
it's just
he he refuses to fail. He refuses to let
things um nothing is going to nothing is
going to u you know is going to dictate
where he goes, what he does, how it's
going to be, he he will dictate to
himself what he's going to do and and uh
it was really yesterday it came down to
you know uh provided nothing happened
today when he woke up you know we did a
workout and quickly it was like I'm
going and we watched him and he was good
and uh was it perfect? No. But he he was
going and nobody was going to talk him
out of not playing. [laughter] I tell
you that. So it was great to have him
out there. And yes, his teammates feed
off of that.
>> Your team now is 15 and0 after a loss in
the last three years. Is there something
about the challenge that they take like
you're talking about St. Brown, but the
challenge that they all take on when
they're kind of up against the wall a
little bit?
>> We just got we need to string some some
wins together now. You know, it's okay.
We we battled back. Got to now we got we
need to get another one. And but um
look, I I just it's kind of where I'd
let off to this this these guys do a
great job of they they take it for what
it is, man. They don't get they don't
get panicked. They don't get panicked.
They don't make something uh out of it
that it's not. Don't make more of it
than it needs to be. There's a reason
why you're not able to win the game. And
here's what it is. And oh, by the way,
is it correctable? Yes, it's
correctable. Well, this is what we got
to do moving forward. where do we find
our matchups versus Dallas for example
on you know in all three phases and
let's play our best game that we played
all year. That's what you're trying to
do. And so I think by doing that and
keeping it that way our guys are able to
always answer back. You know they they
do I think where you get in trouble is
if you start just that you start
panicking and you start oh you know I
gota I got I mentioned this last week.
You got to start doing more than you
need to do. Just do your [clears throat]
job and do it the best you can do it and
make it clean. Make it efficient. Worry
about your fundamentals, your technique,
and and the guy next to you, he'll do
his that because we have the right guys
here.
>> That's the answer to this, but how how
do you replicate it? You know, you got
four games left and especially the
offense has looked like it did for a
long time the last couple years. So, how
do you how do you make sure that this
carries over?
>> Well, we clean up the stuff that bit us
today. That's what we do. Clean up the
stuff that bit us. So, we did some good
things today. That's good. Let's let's
see if we can um tweak a couple of
things and and uh do a version of it,
but also some of these penalties. Let's
cut this out. You know, that that's how
you do it. You just start trying to
reduce the stuff that could cost us. It
didn't today. We were able to overcome
it, but that's that's what you do.
>> Rush uh came up big today. What do you
think allowed them to have so much
success getting Prescott on the ground
and creating those big negative plays?
>> Um there again, I you know, I need to
watch the tape. uh just to see uh
exactly how or what or why. But I know
this, we had a lot of guys who won their
one-on- ons, you know, and uh we were
pretty disruptive there. I already
mentioned Muhammad, you know, I thought
Mack did some good things in there.
Hutch was close a number of times, you
know, and it and he got flushed. Um you
know, and we played pretty good
coverage, you know, it wasn't perfect,
but but all in all, man, we we did what
we had to do and uh we knew we needed to
score on offense. Like I say, it's a
potent offense. Um, and at the end of
the day, we we we did enough in all
three phases.
>> You shifted uh guards back and forth.
Just what was the thinking there? What
did you like out of it going Frasier
alone back?
>> Just to um you know, get get Frasier
some reps. I mean, he's a young guy.
This is about when we uh threw Mahogany
in there last year, Mahogany in there.
Um, and so, you know, we just wanted to
get a look at him and uh, and really he
kind of, you know, it was just to get
him introduced to NFL and try to be
smart and you still want to move the
football, but yet try to set him up to
where he h he can have some success. And
it's, you know, we stayed away from some
plays here. Um, but really he earned the
right to keep going. You know, he did
good enough to where all right, let's
give him another series. Let's uh
because really we didn't have intentions
of giving him as much as he did. We just
wanted to kind of introduce him and and
he did some good things it felt like. So
we did and I thought Cologne did some
dang good things too.
>> Dan, is this a shot yet? You know, he uh
kind of run out of superlatives to talk
about him, but he tied Barry Sanders
record for for most touchdowns by
someone under 24. The way you guys used
him in the passing game, can you just
explain a little bit kind of what he
meant to the offense tonight and and how
dynamic he is to to watch even for you
on the sideline? Yeah, he's he's um you
know, he's unique. [clears throat] He's
special. Um you know, everybody knows
what he can do on the in the run game
and really we couldn't quite get him
going the way we really wanted to in the
run game now. Um but yet he he found he
did find some pay dirt on a couple of
those. Um, but the pass game stuff, he
just continues to grow the more we give
him and the more we work with him. Uh,
in practice, we just continue to try to,
you know,
open his horizons and give him a little
bit more, man. He just grows. He gets
better and better and then he gets in
the game and the routes get crisper and
crisper and he just he just keeps going,
man. There's there's just not a cap on
this this dude yet. And uh and there
again, he works his tail off. He's
freaking smart. He's instinctive. He's a
team guy. I mean, he's something else.
So, the sky's is the limit for him. He's
just getting started now. He's just
getting started.
>> Any idea on branch the severity there?
>> I don't know. I'll know more tomorrow.
Is this a sort of game and the sort of
performance with a essentially a playoff
matchup today that proves not to the
outside world but to your room that this
is the recipe going forward that that
this is a playoff team?
>> Yeah. Well, I mean we we we know what we
are, you know, and and uh I've said it
all along. We can't worry about the
outside noise. We we're the ones who
write our own narrative, man. We're the
ones who know what we are and what it
takes and why we've had some
difficulties, but also why we're able to
succeed. We know why. Um, so, you know,
it's about us and it's about how we
handle our business and we handled our
business today. It was good. And now we
get a little breather. We get we get a
couple of days here to catch our breath
and then we get ready for the Rams.
>> Before you just since he was carded off,
are you concerned it's a long
>> I mean, yeah. I mean, he didn't finish
the game, but there again, I'll know
more tomorrow.
>> Guys, we'll have Jared and Mohamd in
here.
>> Guys, your prior success [music] has put
you at the top of the power rankings
list. That's a good thing, right?
>> Well, just means you've gone from the
underdog to the favorite.
>> But those expectations come from prior
[music] success, so that's okay.
>> What about Cure? Where do you guys rank
on the power list?
>> Actually, we just got named by Forbes as
one of the best car insurance companies
in America.
>> Now, you're the favorite.
>> Guess we have a lot in common. Go cure.
Go Lions.
>> Cure Auto Insurance. Drive well.
>> Detroit Lions Live is brought to you by
Cure Auto Insurance. Log on to cure.com
to see how you can save.
>> Running back Jamir Gibbs now ties Barry
Sanders, one of the greatest of all
time, for the most touchdowns before the
age of 24. He needed 47 Tutties to do
that. J had three touchdowns tonight.
That's the fourth time he's done that in
his career. Lis,
>> no. He's big time. I mean, he's a guy
that you can feed the ball anywhere on
this field, including when you get in
the red zone and get tight down here. He
runs with power. He runs with speed. He
is the ultimate weapon. Congratulations
for tying. One of the greatest to ever
play this game. And look, we still got
how many more games left in this season?
So, you know, he's on a historic pace.
Danny,
>> Jir is one of the best dual threat
running backs in the league with how he
can impact both the run and pass games
at such an elite level. His receiving
game was unleashed tonight. Seven
catches for 77 receiving yards because
for the most part, he was bottled up in
the run game.
>> No, he was. But again, great players
find ways to affect the game. And if he
can't do it running the ball, he can
definitely do it catching the ball. He
is such a mismatch for the opposing
defense. You don't know what or who to
put on him. He linebackers can't cover
him. Safeties can't cover him. I mean,
he is such a mismatch for the opposing
defense. So, it's just so glad. I'm so
happy that we have him as our RB1.
>> He's RB1. You know what? I I think he's
RB1 right now. Let's just call it.
>> We'll call it what it is.
>> Okay. Well, his RB2. I guess it does
feel wrong saying that. David Montgomery
is also a weapon in the run game. He and
Jamir Gibbs have now have now scored a
touchdown in the same game 15 different
times. The only other running back duo
to do that, EMTT Smith and Daryl
Johnston, they did it 14 times. So, the
tandem of Montgomery and Gibbs is now
one of the best in the NFL.
>> It really is. Think about that, Danny.
You talking about a Hall of Famer and
you talking about one of the greatest
fullbacks to ever play this game and
these guys have surpassed them. So, it's
just unbelievable the records that these
guys are uh are breaking and it's just
unbelievable the production that we're
getting out of our backfield. And yeah,
I guess we could call it 1A and 1B
because those guys feed off each other.
We call them Sonic and Knuckles, but
they do feed off each other. I thought
David was big early in this game. kind
of helped loosen up that defense for
what Jir was able to do the do to them
later on in the game.
>> David Montgomery second quarter
touchdown put Detroit up 17-6 in the
first half. Looking at this receiving
game for Detroit, wide receiver Jameson
Williams has another great week here in
week 14. Thanks to his ability to sell
his routes and get get out ahead of
defenders, he was a very reliable
downfield target for Jared Goff tonight.
No, he was. And you know, we didn't know
what we were going to be able to get out
of Almond Rod today, but just thanks to
Jameson for just stepping up. He's
stepped up these last two weeks. He's
been a reliable target uh for Jared
Golf. And when you could get him in
space, the speed is just undeniable. So,
you know, I just love the way we're
utilizing him and those slants, you
know, going across the middle of the
field. you know, it takes courage to
work in that area during a football game
and he's not afraid to go across the
middle. So, he I just think he's
developing and his route tree is
developing
each and every game that we see it and
Jared confidence seems to grow more and
more in Jameson Williams.
>> Amen. Ross St. Brown was questionable
coming into this game. He was injured
last Thursday against the Packers in the
first quarter. Didn't return back to the
game. You didn't know what you were
going to get out of him. Well, tonight
you got 92 receiving yards on six
receptions. And now St. Brown holds the
NFL's most receptions through five
career seasons. Even when you think this
man is down, he is not. Proves to be one
of the best
>> warrior. And Danny, I came up on the
elevator with his pops. Me and dad were
talking. Dad didn't even know what to
expect out of his son today. He is a
warrior to me. He is the heart and soul
of this team. not just the offense, but
of this team. And when he goes, we go.
So, I know the guys were happy, relieved
that Amanro was able to go out there and
still what 70% probably 80% and he's
still putting up those type of numbers.
Again, just so proud of him and I call
him a warrior.
>> Dan Campbell mentioned this was a
complimentary football game. Defense
held their own, especially in that
linebacker core that we talk about week
after week. These two, Jack Campbell and
Derek Barnes, came up clutch in the
takeaway game. Campbell forcing a
fumble. Lions scored a touchdown off of
that. Derek Barnes comes up with a big
interception. Lions convert and score
off of that. These two guys finally are
getting into that takeaway category and
that made the difference tonight.
>> You're exactly right. And when coach say
complimentary football again that gave
the offense these turnovers gave the
offense a short field to work with and
the offense they capitalized off that
short field. So just a great job of
coming up with turnovers something that
we need to flip the field like that. And
Meek Roberts I mean great coverage on
that play. He was the one that deflected
the ball for Derek Barnes to catch that.
So again, it's just nice to see all
three phases of this team play at such a
high level today.
>> This week, defensive back DJ Reid told
me that they are going to deploy a
different method on the best pass
offense in the NFL. When you have two
receivers like CD Lamb and George
Pickkins, you've got to do something
different. DJ Reed was tasked with
trying to contain CD Lamb. You know what
Dak Prescott did? He just kept going
back to Lamb. 121 receiving yards. DJ
Reed, they threw him into the fire, but
you know what? He delivered in the
fourth quarter with that interception to
give his offense back the ball and Jared
Goff was able to put this team into a
victory formation.
>> Yeah, he is not Danny, he took that ball
away on that interception. So, it was
just great to see. I thought Meek played
well. Brian Branch BB man, he is always
playing well. I thought he was the tone
setter back there. But DJ taking on some
of the toughest receivers in this
league, like you say, CD Lamb and George
Pickkins, even uh their tight end, he's
a very good player. But we were able to
slow those guys down just enough for our
offense to continue to put points up.
Sticky defense all game long. And just
the different schemes that Calvin
Shepard came up with, deploying the
linebackers, sending them through the A
gap, dropping back sometime in man,
dropping back sometime in zone. I
thought everybody just played so well on
the defensive side of the ball and it
was gonna take this type of effort to
slow that Dallas Cowboys team down.
>> Defensive tackle or should we call him
defensive end Alen McNeel. He's been
lining up all across that defensive
line. He was able to get in on the sack
party tonight. One sack on Dak Prescott.
Loss of 16 yards for the Cowboys. What
are you seeing out of Mack and the way
he comp commands that interior Dline
>> control Danny that they control the
inside him DJ Reather Roy Lopez Tique
Williams they control the interior of
that Dallas offensive line like you said
Devonte Williams had a tough time
running the ball I know that's what
Dallas wanted to come into the game to
establish him because he has been
running pretty good over the last couple
of weeks but when you have your interior
defensive lineman playing the way our
interior defensive lineman played. They
outshine their big money guys on the
interior. It was just great to see. And
man, that's what we expect out to Dan
and Bear and the rest of his crew in the
middle and they deliver.
>> Quinnon Williams, Kenny Clark were not
the men of the hour, right? It was
Detroit Lions.
>> I mean, I really didn't hear their names
tonight, Danny. And we had a couple of
nice runs up the middle of their
defense. So again, the the three guys on
the inside who taken a lot of criticism,
right, Glam Graham Glascow and, you
know, Tate Ratlitch and all those guys,
they taking a lot. Yeah, exactly. Right.
Having to go in there a rookie, too. So,
I I thought those guys played
complimentary football on the offensive
line, and that's like working like a
hand in the glove. And they did a great
job tonight.
>> We'll get to more of this Detroit Lions
offense. Quarterback Jared Goff is
standing by the podium. When he gets up
there, we'll make sure you hear from QB1
on his big day of securing a Lions win
here inside Ford Field. We'll be right
back after this.
>> Guys, your prior success [music] has put
you at the top of the power rankings
list. That's a good thing, right?
>> Well, just means you've gone [music]
from the underdog to the favorite.
>> But those expectations come from prior
success, so that's okay.
>> What about Cure? [music] Where do you
guys rank on the power list? Actually,
we just got named by Forbes as one of
the best car insurance companies in
America. [music]
>> Now you're the favorite.
>> Guess we have a lot in common.
>> Go Cure.
>> Go Lions.
>> Cure Auto Insurance. Drive well.
>> Detroit Lions Live is brought to you by
Cure Auto Insurance. Log on to cure.com
to see how you can save.
the rookie wide receiver Isaac Tesla.
Welcome. Welcome back to the show, Lis.
In case you missed that,
>> Tesla continues to be an endzone target
for Jared Goff that he can go to. Tesla
fourth touchdown of the season in the
third quarter, capitalizing off of that
Derek Barnes interception that put
Detroit up 27-9. Just two receptions,
averaged 10 yards a catch. What is he
turning into? you know, a a scoring
machine cuz it seemed like all his
catches are for touchdowns. But, you
know, I think it like I always say,
Daniel, a rookie, it's a learning curve
in the NFL. I don't care who you are.
Yes, he's been going through that
learning curve, but now it seems like
that learning curve is speeding up a
little bit more. You could see Dan
Campbell installing him in more plays.
he started tonight. So, you can see him
kind of getting his feet up under him
and they seem to be going to him a
little bit more. Like you say, only two
catches, but one of them were was for a
touchdown. So, he's reliable. And again,
when you get a guy in the end zone, a
big body guy like that that you could
count on when you get close to the end
zone, man, that has to be comforting.
So, I'm I'm liking the way he's starting
to develop, especially as the season
goes along. he won't be considered a
rookie pretty much longer.
>> Hey, and you know, if he continues to
turn out big plays, you deploy him
towards the end zone with J Mo Alman
Ross St. Brown, Jir Gibbs, defenses
don't know who's catching the ball.
>> Come on. And especially with us not
having Sam Leaporter, Brock Wright being
out, us not really having our tight ends
to kind of uh use in that red zone. If
you got receivers that you can deploy
out like that, I think it makes us even
more lethal. Well, some tight ends got
in on the catches as well. Ross Dwelly,
Anthony Friser, hello. Detroit Lions.
Some more pass catchers making their
name here. Detroit, after three games at
home, we've got to go on the road out
west is calling the Detroit Lions and
the LA Rams. With a very familiar face
in quarterback, Matthew Stafford, whose
name is in the MVP race right now. Rams
are in the playoffs as of right now. Of
course, Detroit still in the hunt. The
season ended today. Detroit is not in.
This is another big time NFC matchup.
Lom miss,
>> you know what, Danny? I think we'll
probably be saying this throughout the
rest of this season. A big time game, a
game that we have to have. And no bigger
game than going out to LA and facing uh
Matthew Stafford. A guy that hasn't
beaten us since he's left here. I know
he's chomping at the bit. Like you say,
he's playing at such a high level. He is
a guy that is in the MVP race right now.
And um you know, we're going to have to
probably deploy more of the same of what
we did tonight to get Matthew Stafford
off his spot. He has weapon when you
talking about Devonte that he has out
there and he had Puka Nool out there. So
he has some guys that he has to get the
ball to. And of course his coach Sean
McVey is one of the brightest minds in
this game. So we're going to have
another tall test. But guess what? We
seem to pass those tests every time
they're put up against us and I expect
us to do the same out in LA.
>> I love that Jameson Williams is really
coming on here in the season because his
cousin Kairen Williams first cousin that
is is leading the Rams in that ground
game right now. In Dan Campbell's
presser, he talked a lot about his QB1
Jared Goff. How this offense went
tonight as Jared Jared Goff win tonight.
He refuses to lose and to be beat in
these big time situations. He bounced
back over 300 passing yards today. One
touchdown. That's 19 straight games with
a passing touchdown from this man right
here, Lomis.
>> The smooth operator, as I love the call,
Jared, because again, you never know
when we're up and down with his
expression. But again, like having
another offensive coordinator on the
field, this guy is such a great
competitor. Jared is a great at getting
these guys in the position they need to
be in. He's such a guy that you can look
at across from in the huddle and know
that you have that confidence that if
the game is on the line, if you need a
big throw from this guy, he's going to
make that big throw for you. So, just so
proud of Jared, how he's played this
year. And again, I always say he's so
underrated. People talk about the
weapons that he has around him. Well,
somebody has to get the ball to these
weapons that he has around him. And
Jared's been doing that at a high level
pretty much this whole season.
>> The only chance Goff had to make those
big plays here today was be decisive,
have a quick release with that defensive
line running at him and a banged up O
line. And you saw him adjust to that
fairly quickly there in the first
quarter after some pressures.
>> No, great point, Danny. And look, a lot
of those throws he made, the run, the
wide receivers weren't even out there
cuts and the ball was on the way there.
To me, that's confidence knowing that
your guy's going to be where he's at.
That's timing of knowing that guy going
to be there. That's chemistry from
working with that guy that you know he's
going to be on the spot that he needs to
be on. And Jared was letting it rip. I
mean, he was letting it rip tonight. And
I love to see that because again going
into this part of the season, think
about it, the Rams defense, one of the
top defenses in the league. So he's
going to face even more pressure next
week when we get out to LA. And we're
going to need Jared to be on top of his
game just like he was tonight.
>> QB1 must be singing some Christmas
carols in the locker room because we're
still waiting for him to get to the
podium. You know what? When you play
like that, take your time. Let's take a
look at some upcoming games this
weekend. Detroit of course kicking off
week 14 with a big W and staying in this
one. Dolphins taking on the Jets here at
Sunday 100 p.m. Bears Packers Sunday
that 4:25 slot. That is a major one.
>> Huge game right there. Never thought I
would be pulling for the Green Bay
Packers. Yeah, but I'm I'm pulling for
them on this one, Danny.
>> Oh man. LA Rams. They will take on the
Arizona Cardinals. I That should be an
easy dub for the Rams. However, they did
just lose to the Panthers. No one is
safe right now. Lis,
>> you so right about that. If you don't
come ready to play, you could lose.
>> Commanders, Vikings, another NFC
matchup. Vikings are kind of out of
this. They're out of this thing.
>> They're behind us.
>> They're they're just there's not much to
say to that one. So, this will be a good
slate of G. Sorry about it. Here's some
AFC matchups here. Kansas City Texans.
[clears throat]
That could be a great one on Sunday
Night Football. You never know.
>> The Texans have a great great defense
and Kansas City, they're fighting for
their lives right now.
>> Joey B, Josh Allen will duke it out
Sunday at 100 p.m. I don't know if
that's going to be a good matchup, but I
sure hope it is.
>> You know, I think it will be because
with Joe Burrow being back, man, that's
just a different team.
>> It sure is. Seahawks taking on the
Falcons. Steelers will come to town here
soon. They're taking on Baltimore.
That'll be a good match up.
Yeah, and they're fighting for first
place. I mean, Baltimore is playing a
lot better now, but Pittsburgh, they're
in first place right now. I guess they
want to stay in first place, so they
need to win that game.
>> They sure do. All right, QB1 has
emerged. Let's hear from Jared Goff.
>> Jared, what was what was the the big
message this week? Everybody knew this
was going to be important game, at least
on the outside of the building, but what
was it like on the inside?
>> Yeah, it was it was uh it was good. But
it was it felt like we got back to kind
of who we are early in the week. Um
addressed a lot of what happened in that
Packers game, what went wrong, what
could have done better, and uh I think
you could see a an uptick in urgency
from everybody. Um it was good.
>> You guys uh put the ball in the air a
lot. I think it was just six rushing
attempts after you went up 27 to N. Was
that part of the game plan or is that
[snorts] just kind of how things went?
>> Yeah, part of it. I don't know if we
wanted to be that lopsided, but we
definitely wanted to get after him
through the air and I thought we did.
>> Was um St. Brown as big of a lift?
beyond him being there, but just his
presence as
>> Yeah, I think so. And I think um
obviously his play speaks for itself
tonight, but like bigger than anything
is everyone knowing what he's kind of
dealing with and him being like, I'm
going to be out there and figuring out a
way to get out there and um not many
guys built like him.
>> The stakes of this game just what did
that mean to this league to see him
tough it out?
>> Yeah, it's I mean he's he's he's that
type of guy and it was it was cool to
see him, you know, say like you're not
going to keep me off the field type of
thing. Early in the week though, it was
it was truly I believe 5050 if not if if
not less than that. And as the week went
on, he's like, I'm playing, I'm playing,
I'm playing. And and sure enough, he got
out there, played well.
>> Talk about that play u in the final
minutes where you decided to go to him
and say, you know, the conventional
wisdom is run the ball, take the time
off the clock and everything, but what
was the thinking behind that and how
confident were you in that?
>> Yeah, I loved the call. I really did. It
was I thought that was awesome by Dan.
It, you know, he's our he's our guy and
um the way that they were playing the
run, they were so downhill. You don't
want to wait till third down when they
know you're going to potentially throw
it. you do it on second down and uh it
was a great call. He's wide open and
made a great play.
>> And what he's able to do, man, three
touchdowns. How do you guys, you know,
not take him what he's doing for granted
in the grand scheme of just all the
records he's breaking, everything he's
doing.
>> Yeah. Just speak about him and that guy.
>> It's hard not to take him for granted.
He's he's just he's so good every week
and does a great job uh in everything we
ask him. I think, you know, we would
have probably wanted to get more from
him in the run game. There just wasn't
much there. But the pass game and and
him being able to get in the end zone
was awesome. And I thought Demo ran
incredibly, complimented him really
well. And um when he came in, it was
really good.
>> As well as Alman played as well as I
mean everybody. But just it seemed like
every catch Jameson had was a a drive
extender.
>> Yeah.
>> U his evolution. How much are you
looking for him in those plays?
>> Awesome. It's awesome. It really is.
He's he's becoming that player we always
knew he could be. Um over the course of
this season, he's as reliable as the
guys I've ever played with at this
point. Third down, fourth down, don't
matter. Um he'll make the play, he'll
show up. Um he's an energy guy. He's a
juice guy. He's confident right now.
He's on his details. He's doing
everything right. It's awesome.
>> Another [snorts] new offensive line
combination today. Maybe a little bit of
a rough start for them, but seems like
protection was pretty darn good there in
the second.
>> Yeah, they settled in really nicely. Um
I know they were playing around the left
guard there um with Cologne and Frasier,
but the both guys they settled in
nicely. There were some mistakes
certainly that want to be cleaned up,
but um yeah, for the most part did a
good job.
You guys never at least for three years
lose back-to-back games. And I think
that's not by coincidence. Is it the
uptick in urgency you mentioned? Is it
just by happen stance? What?
>> Um yeah, you know, I I think it is uh a
kind of culmination of who we are. You
know, I I I don't think that happens on
accident. Um I think it was what 15
times now in a row, you know, that's
happened. Um yeah, I don't think it
happens on accident and it's it's who we
are. It's it's what we believe in. Um, I
think, you know, when those losses
happen, they suck. But we we must do a
good as good a job as any team of of
learning from that and coming back the
next week and and putting our head down.
>> There's a debate online right now about
uh the end of the first half play to
Tesla where it's you you kind of had him
open there, but some people think you
were throwing it out of bounds on
purpose and then other people think
maybe you overthrew it. Was there too
much mustard on that one or?
>> Um I mean I don't who's debating like
people on Twitter. Um
>> yeah. So uh if I if I could have had
like a split second longer I would have
thrown in the I would have thrown him a
touchdown. I just wanted to get rid of
the ball at that point. I didn't want to
take a sack. Um if I I I I wanted it
back when I got to the sideline to be
able to put it out there. I was just
throwing it a him or nobody ball. Ended
up being out of bounds. But yeah, I
would have liked to put that in the end
zone. to beat the Cowboys. You guys been
on the island the last three [snorts]
seasons just to actually get them here
in Detroit. How was that for you guys?
>> It was great. It was great. I thought
our fans showed up. It was awesome. It
really was. Um yeah, being able to beat
them. They're as hot as a team as there
is in our league right now. And um you
know, maybe we can become that right
now. I know this is not really the
position you guys want to be in with
some of these losses, but is there I
know this isn't really the position you
guys want to be in with some of these
losses, but is there something about
having your backs to the wall about
every game being a big game that has a
way of elevating the intensity and
bringing out the best in guys?
>> Sure. I I think so. Yeah, I think it
does. And I think, you know, if if we do
this correctly over this last little
stretch of the season, we want to kind
of be doing this right now. Like, okay,
we just scored 44. Our defense played
well. We, you know, won that game. We
want to kind of be on this up ramp by
the time we hit the playoffs where we're
this dangerous team who can kind of go
toe-to-toe with anybody and and that's
what you want and we're right there.
Yeah, if we're able to, you know, win
one at a time, who knows what can
happen. You know, there's plenty there's
plenty of games left and we're playing
well, but sorry to answer your question.
Yes, it does uptick things a little bit
and gives us a little bit more
motivation.
>> Detroit kicks week 14 off with a big
win. Dare we say season saver?
>> Yes. Yes, Danny. That you can say season
saver. That again I say playoff mode.
We're in playoff mode right now. That
was a playoff type of game that we
played today and we came through.
>> Single game elimination is the mindset
going forward according to LB.
>> And can I say one thing? Can we please
give Tom Kennedy some love? I mean
>> he had some fantastic returns.
>> Oh yes he did, Danny. He set us up. I
thought if I had an MVP for the game, it
probably would be Tom Kennedy because of
him where he put us at in field position
time after time after time. So kudos to
you, Tom.
>> Three returns 120 yards.
>> That's awesome.
>> Final thoughts from this 44-30 victory
over the Dallas Cowboys.
>> Danny, a mustwin. We haven't lost backto
back games in probably what 57 games.
There you go. I love that. I think we
tied the New England Patriots. So again,
this team, every time we face adversity,
we know how to deal with adversity and
we come out on the other end of that
adversity. I'm so proud of the guys, the
coaching staff. I'm proud of this whole
stadium because they said come in white.
Look at that big fella. We came in
white. We came in white. It was a white
out. We took care of business. Now on to
the next feat, which is to go out to LA
and get another win. Detroit is going to
have to take care of business against
the Rams. They want to continue to save
their season. It is late. We're going to
get out of here. For Lomus Brown, I'm
Danny Rogers. Hope you enjoyed that
Detroit Lions live postgame show
presented by Curado Insurance. We will
see you on the road week 15 at the LA
Rams. Good night.
Heat. Heat. N.
[music] Heat. Heat. N.